



# Eliecer Sánchez Mora

Date of birth: 05/08/1995 | Nationality: Venezuelan | Gender: Male |

Phone number: (+356) 79548102 (Mobile) | Email address:

eliecer.sanchez47@gmail.com | Website: https://eliecersm-portfolio.netlify.app |

**LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/eliecer-smora-22688a26a

**WhatsApp Messenger:** +356 7954 8102

Address: Triq Had Dingli, Aparment, RBT 9023, Rabat, Malta (Home)

#### **ABOUT ME**

Goal-oriented individual with a pleasant personality and a tenacity that knows no restrictions. I can be a multitasking person, willing to meet the goal of the company and work as a team.

As a Full stack developer, I prefer both frontend and backend, I really like working with JavaScript (libraries, framework (Reactjs and Nodejs), and I keep up learning everyday. Based on my past experience into the programming world, I manage good logic and work under pressure, I am creative and with a positive mentality to solve problems.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

02/10/2023 - CURRENT San Gwan, Malta

### REACT / NEXTJS FRONTEND DEVELOPER KANON GAMING LIMITED

- Develop new pages and features for Casino's websites in Sweden and Denmark using JavaScript, React.js and Next.js. CSS for styles and Firebase.
- Work on Backoffice company for provider's games releases
- Code Improving, Testing, Refactoring, Bugs Fixes, Clean code, Git Actions

02/12/2021 - CURRENT Barquisimeto, Venezuela

### REACTJS AND NODEJS DEVELOPER FREELANCER AND SELF-TAUGHT

- Development with JavaScript library React and developing UI, improving my skills building projects
- Development API, services and more with JavaScript runtime environment NodeJS and it's frameworks

02/01/2022 - 02/04/2022 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

## **JAVASCRIPT** SELF -TAUGHT

- Development and studies of vanilla JavaScript, building small projects

01/05/2018 - 31/08/2018 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

### DATABASE SUPORT AND ADMINISTRATOR (MYSQL) LARA STATE GOBERMENT

- Manage Database for worker assistance system
- Ensure data integrity

01/05/2018 - 01/09/2018 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

### **JAVA SE DEVELOPER** LARA STATE GOBERMENT

- Improve worker assintance system built in Java SE

02/01/2019 – 31/12/2019 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

**JAVA SE DEVELOPER** UNIVERSITY INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY "ANTONIO JOSÉ DE SUCRE" AND THEN FREELANCER

- I have developed an Automated system for managing graduates of my university
- As freelacer i developed an Automated inventory system for a client

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

15/09/2014 - 01/02/2019 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

**UNIVERSITY TECHNICIAN IN COMPUTER SCIENCE** University Institute of Technology "Antonio losé de Sucre"

Website http://www.utsbarguisimeto.edu.ve/

21/08/2016 - 26/10/2016 Baquisimeto, Venezuela

PROGRAMMING LOGIC AND JAVA SE LEVEL 1 COURSE CADIF1

Website https://cadif1.com/

22/11/2017 - 22/03/2019 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

**ENGLISH CONVERSATION 1 COURSE** Westminster

Website https://gelvez.com.ve/barquisimeto/idiomas/27625-idiomas-westminster.html

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **SPANISH** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B2	C1	B2	C1	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

### DIGITAL SKILLS

Reactjs | VisalStudio Code | CSS | React, Next.js, React Native | Version Control System (Git) | CSS | Modules | Tailwind CSS | Git | Postman API | Mongo DB and PostgreSQL | Bootstrap | Nodejs | Socket.io | Express js | Google Firebase, Oracle Cloud Infrastructure | Atlassian stack (Jira, Confluence, ...) | Git, Slack Communication | Version Control Systems: Github | Adatbázis-kezelés (MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Access) | NVM

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

#### **APTITUDES**

Good communication, empathic and work really well within a team

Analytical skills and work well under pressure

Ability to solve problems

Willingness to learn and grow

Having a good business sense

Ability to handle criticism

**Assistance arrange** 

# **REFERENCES**

Mr Luc Young - Lead team Software Developer at Kanon Gaming Limited

Email: luc-young@outlook.com Tlf: +356 7700 9254